Kaleem Mohammad

Web Developer

PERSONAL PROFILE

A confident Software Developer who is ready to face new challenges and eager to explore diverse technologies while collaborating with other IT professionals.

With a goal to one day become a successful senior software developer, I currently have almost 2 years of experience in an Agile environment creating web applications frontend and backend on-site and remote.

EDUCATION

UMUZI

National Certificate in Information Technology (System Development) (SAQA ID 48872) March 2020 - Feb 2021

MANCOSA

NQFL 5 HC Information technology January 2019 - January 2020

TorqueIT

NQFL 4 Technical Support February 2018 - May 2018

Matric

Institute For Quality - 2017

CONTACT AND PORTFOLIO



https://github.com/kaleem99? tab=repositories



https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaleemmohammad-172299147/

PERSONAL WEBSITE

https://kaleem99.github.io/

EMAIL

kaleem1999@outlook.com

Johannesburg Gauteng

EXPERIENCE

Technical support Intern

Gauteng Department Of Education

August 2018 - February 2019

- Network troubleshooting
- Installation of hardware and Software
- · Printer configuration
- · Code up-skilling
- A+ and N+

UMUZI

Web Developer

March 2020- Present

- Write and Review code in node.js/JavaScript and ReactJS
- · collaborating with frontend and backend developers
- · create web applications
- · Syllabus development and maintenance
- modifying and maintaining Tilde, an open-source learning platform
- Mentorship and Pair Programming sessions.

TECH STACK

JavaScript

C Programming

PHP

HTML 5

CSS

SQL

MongoDB

Express JS

React JS

Unit Testing/Test Driven

Development

Cell

0760600653

References:

Ryan: Scrum master/manager

Cell: 074 148 0124

Vuyisanani : Software Developer/manager Cell: 065 171 5910